[
    {
      "question": "What are problems in the complexity class Poly?",
      "answer": "ContainsGAGA, Multiply, SortWords, All3Sets, ShortestPath. - 236"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are problems in the complexity class Expo?",
      "answer": "<Problems from Poly> as well as Factor, MCopiesOfC, AllSubsets, TSPPath. - 236"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is YesOnString and CrashOnString in terms of recognizability and undecidability?",
      "answer": "They are both recognizable but undecidable. - 113"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are examples of problems that are NP-hard but not NP-complete?",
      "answer": "The search variants of SAT and TSP. - 299"
    },
    {
      "question": "How does the moreCsThanGs Turing Machine work?",
      "answer": "Starts left of tape, scan characters one by one, moving to the right. Rejects if there is a left over 'G' if encountered a 'C'. If no C or G is encountered before the x, then reject since there are equal amounts of C's and G's. Accepts if there is a left over 'G' if we encounter a 'C' first. - 81"
    },
      {
      "question": "What is an example of a threshold problem?",
      "answer": "FindShortPath. - 57"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of an optimization problem?",
      "answer": "ShortestPath. - 57"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a search problem?",
      "answer": "FindPath. - 57"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is an example of a function problem?",
      "answer": "Multiply. - 57"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are examples of tractable problems?",
      "answer": "Shortest path, Web search, Error correction. - 4"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which polyreduction requires clause splitting?",
      "answer": "SAT <=P 3-SAT - 288"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which polyreduction requires the Tysetin Transformation?",
      "answer": "CircuitSAT <=P SAT- 287"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are examples of intractable problems?",
      "answer": "Multiple sequence alignment, Decryption. - 4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are examples of uncomputable problems?",
      "answer": "A perfect bug finding program, Solving integer polynomial equations. - 4"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are famous undecidable problems not about programs?",
      "answer": "Diophantine equations, Post correspondence problem, Cellular Automata. - 135"
    }
]